<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>deep-learning on Sérgio - Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://sergiosjs.github.io/tags/deep-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in deep-learning on Sérgio - Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 12:41:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sergiosjs.github.io/tags/deep-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Survey: Open-set Classification</title>
      <link>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_openset/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_openset/</guid>
      <description>Classification is a important field of study in Machine Learning area. Traditional algorithms relay on closed-set scenarios, where the label classes are known in prior. Thus, in real world we eventually deal with unknown instances of data. To treat unseen instances in a proper way, a approach called Openset classification was developed. This paper briefly surveys some of the recent works in Open-set Classification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Report: Exploiting Deep-Features Diversity in Food-11 Classification</title>
      <link>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_food_rep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_food_rep/</guid>
      <description>The best deep representation level is the FC2 deep-feature, contain the most relevant features to classify. Early fusion and Late fusion can&amp;rsquo;t better than only FC2 deep feature. Lastly the Bagging approach achieved the best results of all experiments executed.
The domain of food is hard to classify, even for humans. This happens due to similarity between food made with the same ingredients wich belongs to different classes. Even so the deep feature FC2 showed up a good option and the Bagging technique is the best model.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>