<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jupyter notebook on Sérgio - Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://sergiosjs.github.io/tags/jupyter-notebook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jupyter notebook on Sérgio - Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 12:41:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sergiosjs.github.io/tags/jupyter-notebook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>wiki4HE Exploration, Machine Learning and Storytelling</title>
      <link>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_wiki4he/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_wiki4he/</guid>
      <description>Wiki4HE is a database containing a questionnaire that was applied to teachers with topics regarding their perception of Wikipedia as a tool for other collaborators and students.
Objective of this work:
 Basic statistics on participating teachers Analysis of different user groups for the items “Perceived Enjoyment” ENJ1 and ENJ2 Other interesting analyzes Create a model capable of predicting whether or not a teacher recommends using Wikipedia for his students  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploration of Brazilian federal travel data</title>
      <link>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_travel_br_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_travel_br_2019/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contain four data files:
 Payment (Pagamento): with list of realized payments Ticket (Passagem): purchased tickets Stretch (Trecho): The stretches of the travel Travel (Viagem): Travel itself  In this first part, a descriptive analysis of the data set Travel is performed, grouping the data by various attributes and plotting some graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pokeanalysis and Predicting Legendaries</title>
      <link>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_poke/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_poke/</guid>
      <description>This dataset consist a 721 pokemons of the 1 to 6 Generations, including several features like stats, types, catch rate, if the pokemon is legendary and others, totaling 21 variables. With him we will try to answer the fallowing questions:
 How the amount of pokemons is distributed per generation? Is there missing data in this dataset? Is there any relationship between the type of pokemon and it&amp;rsquo;s color? Which pokemons have the highest attributes values?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survey: Open-set Classification</title>
      <link>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_openset/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_openset/</guid>
      <description>Classification is a important field of study in Machine Learning area. Traditional algorithms relay on closed-set scenarios, where the label classes are known in prior. Thus, in real world we eventually deal with unknown instances of data. To treat unseen instances in a proper way, a approach called Openset classification was developed. This paper briefly surveys some of the recent works in Open-set Classification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Report: Exploiting Deep-Features Diversity in Food-11 Classification</title>
      <link>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_food_rep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergiosjs.github.io/projects/creations/ds_food_rep/</guid>
      <description>The best deep representation level is the FC2 deep-feature, contain the most relevant features to classify. Early fusion and Late fusion can&amp;rsquo;t better than only FC2 deep feature. Lastly the Bagging approach achieved the best results of all experiments executed.
The domain of food is hard to classify, even for humans. This happens due to similarity between food made with the same ingredients wich belongs to different classes. Even so the deep feature FC2 showed up a good option and the Bagging technique is the best model.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>